House of Ga'a is a action, history film directed by Bolanle Austen-Peters.
At the height of the Oyo Empire, the ferocious Bashorun Ga'a became more powerful
than the kings he enthroned, only to be undone by his own blood.
Bashorun Ga'a, played by Femi Branch.
Oyemekun, played by Mike Afolarin.
Ayinba, played by Funke Akindele.
Olukuoye, played by Femi Adebayo.
Sasa L'eniyan, played by Ibrahim Chatta.
Edan Asiko, played by Toyin Abraham.
House of Ga'a is a 2024 Nigerian historical drama film directed by
Bolanle Austen-Peters and written by Tunde Babalola.
It features an ensemble cast including Femi Branch, Bimbo Manuel, Stan Nze,
Lateef Adedimeji, Mike Afolarin, Toyin Abraham and Funke Akindele.